#### Contact

No 194 A, 8th Street, Mahatma Gandhi Nagar, Kolathur, Chennai-99 9003158266 (Work) sivainspy@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sivakumar-dayalan-115b3797 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Hadoop

Hive

Spark

#### Languages

Tamil (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

#### Certifications

Certified Associate in Software Testing (CAST)

#### Honors-Awards

Performer of the Year

# Sivakumar Dayalan

Senior Software Engineer at Tech Mahindra

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

# Summary

Application Developer who worked in Big Data Environment, where its ecosystem comprises of Hadoop, Hive, Spark, Oozie, Sqoop, Solr, NiFi, MySQL and other industrial technologies like Shell Scripting, Control-M, Teradata, MongoDB, Python, Java, Selenium and JMeter.

## Experience

Tech Mahindra Senior Software Engineer May 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Amtex Software Solutions Pvt Ltd Associate Consultant Senior Test Engineer July 2017 - May 2019 (1 year 11 months) Chennai

Hadoop/Big Data Testing and Deployment in IoT

Scientific Publishing Services Pvt Ltd Technical Editor November 2014 - July 2017 (2 years 9 months) Chennai

Microsoft Word Tool (WEST), Manual Testing, VB Scripting, PMS, XML, HTML

Deccan iServices Pvt Ltd XML Programmer October 2013 - July 2014 (10 months) Chennai

APTARA XML Tool Testing, Error Handling, Defect Log, XML, HTML

Cal C Soft Pvt Ltd
Process Executive
September 2012 - September 2013 (1 year 1 month)

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Proof Reading, PDF Creation, PDF Compare, Kindle, MS Word, Abby Fine Reader, HTML Layout

# Education

S. A. Engineering College

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Computer Science · (2009 - 2012)

Murugappa Polytechnic College, Avadi

DECE, Electronics and Communication Engineering · (2006 - 2009)